Hey guys! I saw this catsuit on sale at Maison Catanzaro and I thought wow I
have to try it because look at this cut and look at these panels it's just bound
to be so good so I received it and I can't wait to try it on let's get changed
I got into it it was a bit tricky to be honest because there is no long back
zip and you can't really completely unzip the front zip but I managed and
here I am and I have to say it fits really good and I love the back so
excuse me if I just standing like this now talking to you while showing my back
because I think the cut and the back of this catsuit is superior I mean we have
these kind of like panty silhouette here which also to be honest is in the front
too but it just fits so good we have the cross zipper which runs into the back
and I think it makes it great booty
as for the front I'm mostly too tall for a lot of products and catsuits so what I
also do to accentuate my waist a bit better is getting one of the most used
accessories here, my metal belt. Just have to figure it out how. Let me turn it around.
Yeah, like this.
I started with some classy pleaser open heels.
And the material is kind of like in between.
So it's not as shiny as normal PVC, so to say, like the shoes, for example.
It's more matte, but it's also like really thick.
And for leather, it's too smooth.
So it's really unique.
I kind of love the look. It's not too shiny, a bit more subtle, but kind of classy this way.
This catsuit has so many panels, individual pieces sewn together. It's insane. Also the
design here with the zipper and the keyhole. You can open and close the zippers a bit more.
I could maybe close this more and open this one more.
I think I prefer the other way around.
Closing this, it is a bit more open.
And I also love that the arms are long enough and the legs are long enough.
Like really long, no problem at all. Love this.
When I opened the package, there was a surprise.
Inside Kamisawa also sent me this dress along.
It's from the same series. It's the same material. It has the same kind of cool silver zippers
And I want to show it too, so I will change into it
I have to check if the zippers are the same height
height? height? height? height? because of course you can open them and
Then you can basically show what you wear underneath or don't wear
It's kind of a fetish dress, you can play with it and yeah it's the same material.
I like it.
I like little black dresses.
This is the back side.
Of course if you don't want to have the zippers right here in the middle you can also move
them to here.
Then they're not that much on display.
But I mean you can also hold them to the pier.
That's also nice.
I have to say it gives it kind of an edge when they're here in the middle.
But this is also a nice option.
And yeah, I'm wearing size small by the way in the dress and the catsuit.
I think both is still available by the time I'm recording this video.
I don't know if it will be available when I publish this video, but you can check out Maison Karazawa.
I will put the link in the description text.
I think this one looks from the back nice too.
Tell me in the comments what's your preferred option, the catsuit or the dress.
Let me know.
Also, don't forget to click on the thumbs up for this video.
Check out my Patreon and my social medias.
the links I put in the description text and I will see you in the next video
hope you enjoyed this one have a nice day bye